Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 3. Personal, Political and Official Files, 1944-2010 TJU.2010.01.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Schedules, 1981-2010; V.
  - Schedules, February 1999 (Box 545, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, March 1999 (Box 545, Folder 2-5)
  - Schedules, April 1999 (Box 545, Folder 6-8)
  - Schedules, May 1999 (Box 545, Folder 9-11)
  - Schedules, June 1999 (Box 545, Folder 12-14)
  - Schedules, July 1999 (Box 545, Folder 15-16)
  - Schedules, August 1999 (Box 545, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, September 1999 (Box 545, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, October 1999 (Box 546, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, November 1999 (Box 546, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, December 1999 (Box 546, Folder 3)
  - Appointment book, 1999 (Box 546, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, January 2000 (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, February 2000 (Box 546, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, March 2000 (Box 546, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, April 2000 (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, May 2000 (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, June 2000 (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, July 2000 (Box 546, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, August 2000 (Box 546, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, September 2000 (Box 546, Folder 14-15)
  - Schedules, October 2000 (Box 546, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, November 2000 (Box 546, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, December 2000 (Box 546, Folder 18)
  - Appointment book, 2000 (Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, January 2001 (Box 547, Folder 2-3)
  - Schedules, February 2001 (Box 547, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, March 2001 (Box 547, Folder 6-8)
  - Schedules, April 2001 (Box 547, Folder 9-10)
  - Schedules, May 2001 (Box 547, Folder 11-13)
  - Schedules, June 2001 (Box 547, Folder 14-16)
  - Schedules, July 2001 (Box 548, Folder 1-3)
  - Schedules, August 2001 (Box 548, Folder 4-5)
  - Schedules, September 2001 (Box 548, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, October 2001 (Box 548, Folder 8-11)
  - Schedules, November 2001 (Box 548, Folder 12-13)
  - Schedules, December 2001 (Box 548, Folder 14-15)
  - Schedules, January 2002 (Box 548, Folder 16-17)
  - Schedules, February 2002 (Box 549, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, March 2002 (Box 549, Folder 3-4)
  - Schedules, April 2002 (Box 549, Folder 5-6)
  - Schedules, May 2002 (Box 549, Folder 7-9)
  - Schedules, June 2002 (Box 549, Folder 10-11)
  - Schedules, July 2002 (Box 549, Folder 12-14)
  - Schedules, August 2002 (Box 549, Folder 15-16)
  - Schedules, September 2002 (Box 549, Folder 17-18)
  - Schedules, September 2002 (Box 550, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, October 2002 (Box 550, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, November 2002 (Box 550, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, December 2002 (Box 550, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, January 2003 (Box 550, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, February 2003 (Box 550, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, March 2003 (Box 550, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, April 2003 (Box 550, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, May 2003 (Box 550, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, June 2003 (Box 550, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, July 2003 (Box 550, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, August 2003 (Box 550, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, September 2003 (Box 550, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, October 2003 (Box 550, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, November 2003 (Box 550, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, December 2003 (Box 550, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, January 2004 (Box 550, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, February 2004 (Box 550, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, March 2004 (Box 550, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, April 2004 (Box 550, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, May 2004 (Box 550, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, June 2004 (Box 550, Folder 22)
  - Schedules, July 2004 (Box 550, Folder 23)
  - Schedules, August 2004 (Box 550, Folder 24)
  - Schedules, September 2004 (Box 550, Folder 25)
  - Schedules, October 2004 (Box 551, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, November 2004 (Box 551, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, December 2004 (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, January 2005 (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, February 2005 (Box 551, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, March 2005 (Box 551, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, April 2005 (Box 551, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, May 2005 (Box 551, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, June 2005 (Box 551, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, July 2005 (Box 551, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, August 2005 (Box 551, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, September 2005 (Box 551, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, October 2005 (Box 551, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, November 2005 (Box 551, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, December 2005 (Box 551, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, January 2006 (Box 551, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, February 2006 (Box 551, Folder 17)
  - Schedules, March 2006 (Box 551, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, April 2006 (Box 551, Folder 19)
  - Schedules, May 2006 (Box 551, Folder 20)
  - Schedules, June 2006 (Box 551, Folder 21)
  - Schedules, July 2006 (Box 551, Folder 22)
  - Schedules, August 2006 (Box 551, Folder 23)
  - Schedules, September 2006 (Box 551, Folder 24)
  - Schedules, October 2006 (Box 551, Folder 25)
  - Schedules, November 2006 (Box 551, Folder 26)
  - Schedules, December 2006 (Box 551, Folder 27)
  - Schedules, January 2007 (Box 551, Folder 28)
  - Schedules, February 2007 (Box 551, Folder 29)
  - Schedules, March 2007 (Box 551, Folder 30)
  - Schedules, April 2007 (Box 551, Folder 31)
  - Schedules, May 2007 (Box 551, Folder 32)
  - Schedules, June 2007 (Box 551, Folder 33)
  - Schedules, July 2007 (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Schedules, August 2007 (Box 552, Folder 2)
  - Schedules, September 2007 (Box 552, Folder 3)
  - Schedules, October 2007 (Box 552, Folder 4)
  - Schedules, November 2007 (Box 552, Folder 5-6)
  - Schedules, December 2007 (Box 552, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, January 2008 (Box 552, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, February 2008 (Box 552, Folder 9-10)
  - Schedules, March 2008 (Box 552, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, April 2008 (Box 552, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, May 2008 (Box 552, Folder 13)
  - Schedules, June 2008 (Box 552, Folder 14)
  - Schedules, July 2008 (Box 552, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, August 2008 (Box 552, Folder 16)
  - Schedules, September 2008 (Box 552, Folder 17-18)
  - Schedules, October 2008 (Box 553, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, November 2008 (Box 553, Folder 3-4)
  - Schedules, December 2008 (Box 553, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, January 2009 (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Schedules, February 2009 (Box 553, Folder 7-8)
  - Schedules, March 2009 (Box 553, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, April 2009 (Box 553, Folder 10-11)
  - Schedules, May 2009 (Box 553, Folder 12)
  - Schedules, June 2009 (Box 553, Folder 13-14)
  - Schedules, July 2009 (Box 553, Folder 15)
  - Schedules, August 2009 (Box 553, Folder 16-17)
  - Schedules, September 2009 (Box 553, Folder 18)
  - Schedules, October 2009 (Box 554, Folder 1-2)
  - Schedules, November 2009 (Box 554, Folder 3-4)
  - Schedules, December 2009 (Box 554, Folder 5)
  - Schedules, January 2010 (Box 554, Folder 6-7)
  - Schedules, February 2010 (Box 554, Folder 8)
  - Schedules, March 2010 (Box 554, Folder 9)
  - Schedules, April 2010 (Box 554, Folder 10-11)
  - Schedules, May 2010 (Box 554, Folder 12-13)
- VIP Mail, 1981-2010; VI.
  VIP Mail contains correspondence to and from individuals identified in the office as VIPs. This includes correspondence with past and sitting presidents, members of Congress, celebrity figures, business leaders, foreign dignitaries, and state and local officials, among others. "Dear Colleagues" letters written in a professional capacity to officially convey stances to Senatorial colleagues are also included here. Material in this series is arranged chronologically, separated into folders for ingoing and outgoing mail.
  - January 1981-September 1982 (Box 555)
  - October 1982-October 1983 (Box 556)
  - November 1983-October 1984 (Box 557)
  - November 1984-December 1985 (Box 558)
  - January 1986-April 1988 (Box 559)
  - May 1988-December 1989 (Box 560)
  - January 1990-May 1992 (Box 561)
  - June 1992-October 1993 (Box 562)
  - November 1993-July 1994 (Box 563)
  - August 1994-March 1995 (Box 564)
  - April 1995-January 1996 (Box 565)
  - February 1996-March 1997 (Box 566)
  - April 1997-August 1998 (Box 567)
  - September 1998-March 2001 (Box 568)
  - April 2001-November 2002 (Box 569)
  - December 2002-January 2005 (Box 570)
  - February 2005-September 2006 (Box 571)
  - October 2006-September 2008 (Box 572)
  - October 2008-October 2010 and undated (Box 573)